the fact that he tried to Well, okay,
тот факт что как бы он пытался Ну ладно
cut out, let's say, both the Russian-speaking
вырезать скажем так и русскоязычное
population and the Polish and the Jewish population where And where,
население и польское и еврей где А где
where, look, where he was going to cut out the
где смотри где он собирался вырезать
Russian-speaking population if there was
русскоязычное население если там где жил
no Russian-speaking population where Bandera lived,
Бандера русскоязычного населения не
why was there a soldier Good evening
было почему был солда добрый вечер
Hello, I am from the city of Khmelnitsky,
Здравствуйте я из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine  Where are you from Girls
Украина Вы откуда Девушки
Saint Petersburg you are from Saint Petersburg Well yes Pony
санкт-петербург вы Питерские Ну да Поня
herself is from Saint Petersburg or came to
са м из Питера или где-то приехали
study somewhere originally from Saint Petersburg I understood how it is
учиться родом из Питера понял как там у
there White Nights yes Or as they say
вас там Белые ночи да Или как говорят
Saint Petersburg Well yes already how are things cold
Питер Ну уже да свята как дела холодно
cold And support the special operation
холодно А спецоперацию
let's be  let's have a good
поддержите давай будем давай хорошем на
special operation on the white nights now And what is
белых ночах сейчас спецоперацию А что у
written on your T-shirt in runes some kind of
вас на футболке написано рунами какая-то
Nazi my God and what is a Nazi
наци ми Бог а что такое нацистское
salute Why I don't know I'm
приветствие Почему я не в курсе Я
asking Well some no it's just
спрашиваю Ну какие-то нет это просто
Russia was with us Well it's just those
Россия с нами было Ну просто вот эти там
Nazis there  They love all sorts of runes. That's what they
нацисты они руны любят всякие Вот какие
are. And pagans are also Nazis. Come on,
а язычники язычники тоже нацисты Да ну
he's Hitler.  worshiped too there is a
Гитлер он же поклонялся тоже там
swastika sun yes like well I'm
свастика солнце да типа ну я же сейчас
not saying anything about what's there And you you
ничего не говорю про то что там А вы вы
you you are a
вы вы
pagan no it's just written in runes
язычница нет это просто рунами написано
I don't understand Listen and this and you are very
Я не понима Слушайте а это а вы очень
similar I just Look I just asked
похожи Я просто Смотри я просто спросил
or are you like with runes  I don't know, it's the first
или вы типа с рунами я же не знаю первый
time I've seen a girl with
раз вижу девушку с
runes. I have no language for the semantic load.
рунами у меня язы смысловой нагрузки
Yeah, I get it, it's cool. I see. And you're a Streamer. Yes,
просто Ага понял прикольно Понятно А вы
Streamer. What's up?
Стример Да Стример что как там всем
Say hello to all the subscribers. How do
привет передай привет подпищникам Так
you feel about
как вы относитесь к
the special operation?
спецоперации с
I don't
кайфом Я не знаю
know. Well, what do you think is right?  that
знать Ну как вы считаете правильно что
Russia is killing people in Ukraine Why
Россия убивает людей в Украине Почему
who is it killing in Ukraine Oh my God
кого она убивает в Украине О боже
Well if you ask Listen I'm
ощ Ну если ты спрашиваешь Слушай я
now if I go deeper into the history of
сейчас если буду углубляться в историю с
Euromaidan then this how do you
Евромайдана потом этот как вы там
say bambas Donbass this can
выражаетесь бамбас Донбасс это можно из
be from this or from what do you want to go From
этого пойти или с чего ты хочешь пойди С
what  do you want to tell me is it right for
чего хочешь скажи Правильно ли делать
Russia to do what it does, it is killing people in Ukraine, it is
Россия что убивает людей в Украине она
not killing people in Ukraine, they are
не убивает людей на Украине они сами
dying themselves, yes,
умирают да да
it is just firing shells, and  people die themselves
она просто выпускает снаряды а люди сами
yes Well
да Ну
listen You are
слушай Ты сейчас
trying now I have my own point of view
пытаешься У меня есть своя точка зрения
on this I think that firstly Yes since
на это я считаю что во-первых Да так как
you now want to join NATO well I
Вы сейчас хотите вступить в НАТО а ну
understand that Volodya doesn't like it
сам понимаю что Володе это не нравится
when some post-Soviet state
когда какое-то постсоветское государство
joins it I  I don't ask did you join
туда вступает Я же не спрашиваю вступил
didn't join here people are being killed in
не вступил вот людей убивают в Украине
Ukraine So you are not people in Ukraine you are not Look
Так вы не людей на Украине вы не Смотри
I had a guy from Donbass who
у меня тебя был челик с Донбасса который
wait again look here you came
подожди ещё раз смотри вот вы так пришли
and kill people in Ukraine you
и убиваете людей в Украине
are killing specifically me yes Oh yeah I am
убиваете конкретно я да А ну да я
specifically  yes That is you people in Ukraine
конкретно да То есть вы людей в Украине
yes specifically me yes yes specifically you too
да конкретно я да да конкретно вы тоже
yes and also and support this
да ещё ещё и поддерживаете это
Yes
Да
legitimization well what is it
легитимизация ну что это
clear Well okay next question What
понятно Ну хорошо дальше вопрос Что
is legitimization well like
такое легитимизация хорошо типа
support you support Yes for me here is a
поддержка ти поддержка Да для меня здесь
translation Let me talk to a smart girlfriend
перево Давай я с умной подружкой
better and I will refrain complain
поговорю лучше а я воздержусь пожаловать
opinion Yes she is politically correct no no
мнение Да она политкорректно не не
Wait she is studying to be some kind of lawyer
Подожди она ведь на какого-то юриста
or whoever no architecture
учится или на кого нет на архитек
let me talk to the architect And
давайте я с архитектором поговорю А вы
who are you studying to be  I work All Let me
на кого учитесь Я работаю Всё Давайте я
talk to the student and you work
со студенткой поговорю а вы работаете
hello Yes Good afternoon My name is
здравствуйте Да Добрый день Меня зовут
Andrey What is your name and will there be
Андрей Вас как зовут а а в тиктоке будут
all these videos on TikTok Will be will be Yes I
эти всякие видосики Будет будет Да я
just want to watch it later ok
просто хочу потом это посмотреть хорошо
yes let me talk to the architect for
да давайте я с архитектором поговорю на
a minute What is your name  once again Anya Anya
минутку Как вас зовут ещё раз Аня Аня
Anya Do you think it's normal that
Аня Как вы считаете это нормально что
Russia is killing people in Ukraine so
Россия убивает людей в Украине так вот
I'll probably refrain from giving an opinion
это я воздержусь пожалуй от мнения
because I really can't
потому что я на самом деле не могу
accept any absolutely
принять какую-то прям абсолютно точно
exact point of view
точ какую-то конкретную точку мнения
because the point of view  Lord,
потому что точку зрения Господи
since all the information in principle
поскольку а вся информация в принципе
probably that comes in it can't
наверное которая поступает она не может
be
быть
uh it can't be verified probably in
э не может быть проверенной наверное в
general I'll probably borrow some I'll
общем я наверное займу какой-то
abstain Okay, in short, so look no
воздержусь Ладно короче так смотрите не
no Wait, wait, I'm not saying
не Подожди подожди я я а не до говорю
Look That is, it turns out Maybe then it's
Смотри То есть получается Может тогда
logical  that your state would have first
логично что ваше государство Сначала вам
informed you and then would have attacked
донеслось а потом бы уже нападала на
Ukraine Yes And so it attacks and kills
Украину Да А так она нападает убивает
people you don't understand why it kills
людей вы не понимаете почему она убивает
people we haven't figured it out we don't have information
людей мы не разобрались у нас нет инфор
I think of course  can't help but
Я считаю конечно же не может не
worry any person in principle
тревожить в принципе любого человека не
can't help but T the fact that in principle
может не Т факт того что в принципе идут
any military actions are taking place doesn't
какие-либо боевые действия меня не
suit me Okay listen look
устраивает Хорошо слушай смотри 21
January 21 oh this February yes When Russia
января ой этого февраля да Когда Россия
finally declared the DPR and n
вс-таки провозгласила ДНР и н
independent and well independently from the
самостоятельными и ну самостоятельно от
Ukrainian  states They were considered
украино государствами Они же считались
our allies Yes, and in this
на нашими союзными Да вот и в этот
period Oops to myself Here it is, it seems, all the
период Опа себе Вот он походу всё свет
lights are blinking at you yes yes yes everything is in St. Petersburg
свет мигает у вас да да да всё в Питере
sve We are in secret with you, you are green there next to you
све Мы же вти вас же у вас же зеле там
la well, in short, look at this
рядом ля а ну вот короче смотри вот за
these 3 days in these 3 days Ukraine has inflicted
эти 3 дня за эти 3 дня Украина нанесла
there more than 2,000 some artillery
там более 2.000 каких-то артиллерийских
how do you know this something that
откуда вы это знаете что то есть только
was just there we didn't figure it out And now we've
что были не разобрались А теперь уже вс
figured it out 200,000 there were 200 strikes no
разобрались 200000 там ударов 200 не
less but the
поменьше но
matter is you will answer
дело ответишь
that you will answer for the bazaar come on and what Well
что ответишь за базар давай а что Ну за
you will answer for your words For what for this that
базар ответишь За какой за вот это что
Ukraine carried out 2000 shellings there Well,
Украина там 2000 обстрелов сделала Ну а
no Well, if you don't answer your mouth  opening 2014
нет Ну если не ответишь рот открыва 2014
answer
отве
Well in the source that is one source In
Ну в источнике то есть одного источни В
which source to
каком источнике
read not me honestly I already read about the fact
прочитать не я честно я уже читаю про то
that everything there is set against Russia can
что там всё настроено против России кани
read which source You read Here
прочитать какий источник Ты читаешь Вот
you What sources do you
ты Какие источники
read
читаешь
news on which site in the cam channel
новости каком сайте в кам канале
that was Was inflicted  a blow in these 3 days
то что была Был нанесён удар в эти 3 дня
from the 2nd to whatever date this is a fact here I am telling
с 2 по чее число это факт вот я говорю
you this fact where do you read Here is where you
ты этот факт где ты читаешь Вот где ты
read the news do you watch Solovyov's TV
читаешь новости телевизор Соловьёва
or some Telegram channel
смотришь или какой-то Telegram канал Вот
Tell me the name of the source even if Well
скажи название источника даже если Ну
even Listen Even if and Solovyov's channel
даже Слушай Даже если и канал Соловьёва
Well  just tell me Name the sources
Ну вот скажи просто Назови источники в
you get your information from I'm
которых ты берёшь информацию Мне
interested
интересно
just come on Listen well I don't know if
просто давай Слушай ну я не знаю если
you click Rus Life Okay in Telegram R Life what is
тыкаешь Rus Life Окей в телеге R Life
it in Telegram Yes yes yes well who is
это что в телеге Да да да нуй кто кто
running this Rus Life I just That is
ведёт эту Rus Life я я просто То есть
it's just anonymous  channel yes yes So
это просто анонимный канал да да Так
listen and what are you just Wait wait
слушай а ты что просто Подожди подожди
That is if anonymous Wait if
То есть если анонимный Подожди если
anonymous channel writes that you for example
анонимный канал напишет что ты например
it will be
это будет
true yes  I will dispute who what how
правда да я буду оспаривать кому что как
it is an anonymous channel you can write
это анонимный канал там можно писать что
anything there nonsense Well, okay, look, I'll say it in short
угодно бред А ну хорошо смотри я короче
Look, now we have a channel What's your
Смотри сейчас есть у нас канал Как тебя
name by the way, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter Yes, now
зовут кстати неважно неважно Да сейчас
on Google there is a channel of Peter, here is
на гуглю так есть канал Питера вот есть
your photo, it
твоя фотка это что ты
turns out that you are Well  listen what's going on here Well
получается Ну слушай вот причём зде Ну
look I went in there's a Telegram
смотри вот я зашёл есть такой Telegram
channel it
канал
says anonymous channel can't do it
пишет анонимный канал не может обва
today Today
сегодня Сегодня
I watched about that Wagner from Bakhmut they
смотрела про то то Вагнер из бахмута
left they will leave on the tenth this is
вышли будут выходить десятого числа это
reliable information this is
же достоверная информация это
reliable information pomo Yes where are you from
достоверная информация пому Да откуда ты
where well like who even  tick so that it
где ну как бы кто доже галочку чтобы это
would be Prigozhin, I am the one saying Come on, let
бы Пригожин именно я я говор Давай давай
me
я с умной
talk to a smart one It's better that way Yes, yes, look And
поговорю Так лучше Да да смотрите А вы
from what sources do you get information
вот с каких источников берёте информацию
she is not interested in this I have completely moved away
она этим не увлекается я пос отошла
from this Well, maybe the last
вообще от этого Ну последние может быть
two months I have practically stopped
месяца два Я практически перестала
watching any  or in general But I don't know
смотреть какие-либо вообще А вот не знаю
it turned into some kind of White noise
это превратилось в какой-то Белый шум
and A ok but for example according to your
и А хорошо а вот например по вашим
estimates How many people have already died in
оценкам Сколько уже погибло людей в
Ukraine from this war Well, no, it's clear
Украине от этой войны Да не ну понятно
that  a lot and it is clear that this is all very
что много и понятно что это всё очень
bad How many exactly Well I don't know
плохо Сколько именно Ну не знаю
probably I think that thousands maybe
наверное я думаю что тысяч может быть
even 40 or 50 Yes no Yes if in
даже уже 40 или 50 Да нет Да если в
one Mariupol Only 500,000
одном Мариуполе Только 500 000
half a million lived not Listen if you
полмиллиона жило не Слушай вот если вот
rely on this Yes on all this
так вот опираться Да на всё это
information  it's clear And as if every
информацию это понятно И как бы каждый
citizen Yes there is their own country everyone has
гражданин Да там своей страны у каждого
their own truth I also as if we also have
своя правда я тоже как бы у нас тоже
problems because of this and our relatives
из-за этого проблемы и наши родственники
there friends this is all also there And as if you
там друзья это все тоже там И как бы
understand this is a war of the authorities not in the
понимаешь это же это война властей не в
sense of relatives living  in Ukraine or are
смысле родственники живут в Украине или
they fighting in Ukraine no no I have friends
воюют в Украине не не у меня есть друзья
in Ukraine but I don't communicate with them
на Украине но я с ними не общаюсь потому
because I
что я
Well of course like any other person that I
Ну конечно как и Любой человек что я
understand And what do your friends tell you for
понимаю А что тебе друзья говорят вот
example well what is happening in Ukraine we
например ну что происходит в Украине мы
don't talk about it we  we don't talk about it
об этом не говорим мы об этом не говорим
I because well I don't want to and Okay look
Я потому что ну не хочу а Хорошо смотри
who you trust more anonymously
кому ты больше доверяешь анонимно
Telegram channel or friends from Ukraine I'll
Telegram каналу или друзьям из Украины Я
even tell you honestly
даже честно я тебе так скажу
that when it all
что когда это всё
started and Well I don't know at all it was like
началось и Ну не знаю вообще было типа
what she wrote to me like as I remember
какого она мне написала типа как помню
Yes, such a war has begun Bro, I'm like, why is
Да такая Бро война началась я такая чего
that all  the first these videos No, it's not that
вот все первые эти видео Да не это
terrible then some information from
ужасно потом какая-то информация от
Russian television Well or
российского телевидения Ну или
television just mass media
телевидения просто массовой информации
through the media
через средства массовой информации
some from Ukraine you there let's say
какая-то из Украины ты там допустим
look listen what well there is not hi
смотри послушаешь что ну там не хи
cardia has begun Listen to those
кардия началась Вот послушаешь там тех
who came from the front  they say that let's say
кто пришёл с фронта говорят что допустим
the same Ukrainians I'm telling you from words I
те же украинцы я тебе со слов говорю
know the same Ukrainians are also very
знаком те же украинцы тоже очень
brutal and they
зверские какие-то там и гражданским
give weapons to civilians and Well, in short,
выдают оружие и Ну короче что они выдают
what is bad about them giving weapons Well, to kill the
оружие это что плохо Ну чтобы убивать
occupiers who come to kill us is
оккупантов которые прилет убить нас это
normal, defense and attack
же нормально защита и нападение
once let's sleep Let's think again Dava
раз давай сно Давай снова на ум Дава
lover already found himself in such an environment in
ловек уже оказался в такой среде при
which he already nothing Can send there is
которой он уже ничего Может слать есть
s and
сй и
this tsya just silently there continue to
этой тся просто молча там продолжать
do there what he did roughly speaking
делать там то что он делал грубо говоря
and give not to give the appearance because that's
и подавать не подавать виду потому
what another your girlfriend is
что вот какой другой ваша подружка
novskogo city here in Ukraine which
новского города вот в Украине которая
called you it doesn't matter I don't want I want to
вам звонила неважно не хочу я хочу
understand
понять
just Ukraine Yes she
просто Украина Да вот она там вам
told you there are some Nazis there
рассказывала есть там какие-то нацисты
or something
прям или что-то
like that I didn't ask
такое не спрашивала
but Nazis are everywhere It seems to me just
но нацист есть везде Мне кажется просто
like  it's understandable you
как бы понятное дело
just understand Bandera is watching about
Просто понимаешь Вот про
the Nazis
нацистов вот
and how do you
смотрит Бандера Да а ты вот как
feel about
относишься к
Bandera yours I'm asking I think I
бандере сваю Я спрашиваю Я считаю я
think Bandera is a fighter for the independence of
считаю бандеру борцом за независимость
Ukraine Yes we name streets after him
Украины Да у нас называют улицы Его
Well that's Bandera for the
именем Ну ито такой Бандера для
people who also served there during the war
зна который в годы войны там тоже
Hitler And what do you mean
послужил Гитлеру И что в смысле послужил
he served he was a citizen of Poland and the
он вообще гражданином Польши был а
Soviet Union attacked Poland together with Hitler
Советский Союз напал вместе с Гитлером
and tore Poland apart no
на Польшу и разорвали Польшу на части не
that yes It was at that time he was born in
это да Это на тот момент он родился в
Poland Yes he was born in
Польше Да он родился ещё в
Austria-Hungary then once AST Hungary
австро-венгрии потом раз АСТ Венгер
fell apart Well  it's complicated like very much in
распалась Ну это сложно типа очень
short Poland
короче появилась Польша
Ukraine West Ukrainian People's
Украина западно-украинская народная
Republic appeared there Czechoslovakia and a number of other
республика там Чехословакия ещё там ряд
countries there okay so hard well let's skip
стран хорошо так тяжело ну пропустим
this moment
этот момент
danim I'm talking about it I watched the film Well I was
даним я про него Фильм смотрела Ну мне
interested in it in general just that
интересно было вообще просто вот тот
fact I don't know eh History is a long time ago But
факт я не знаю э История это давно Но
that  the fact that he tried to Well, okay,
тот факт что как бы он пытался Ну ладно
cut out, let's say, both the Russian-speaking
вырезать скажем так и русскоязычное
population and the Polish and Jewish where And
население и польское и еврейское где А
where, where, look where he was going to cut out
где где смотри где он собирался вырезать
Russian-speaking population if there
русскоязычное населения если там где жил
was no Russian-speaking population where Bandera lived
Бандера русскоязычного населения не было
Well, he was against the communists
Ну так он же против коммуни коммунистов
too,
тоже ещё раз
look again Bandera lived in Western Ukraine
смотри Бандера жил на Западной Украине
which was the territory of
которая была территория там
Austria-Hungary, yes, before that there
австро-венгрии да до этого так там
were no Russian-speaking people there, there were no Russians
русскоязычных не было русских не было
there Well, cut them out then, well  how can you
там Ну вырезать тогда ну как можно
cut out those who are
вырезать тех кого там
not there No I mean on the territory of the
нет Нет я имею в виду на территории
Yes he was on the territory of Western
самой Да он был на территории Западной
Ukraine but they somehow
Украины но они же как-то
could not stand it Bandera you understand Bandera
выдержали Бандера вы поняли Бандера
was born such Bandera in the village of old
народився такий Бандера в сели старый
Ugnevo Frankiv on Frankiv we think something
угнев франкив на франкив думаем что-то
shorter  there are a lot of Russians and
короче тут дуже багато россиян и
Russian languages here in my old eels
росийсько мовни в мене в старому угри
Let me cut out the guy I
Давай я х буду вырезать хлопцем
wonder what kind of Russians and
интересно да каких русских и
Russian-speaking people Bandera wanted to cut out Yes
русскоязычных Бандера хотел вырезать Да
where there were no Russians and Russian-speaking people
там где русских и русскоязычных не
except for the occupiers who came
было кроме как оккупантов которые пришли
BN Well, this is [ __ ] awesome the most important thing Yes,
БН Не ну это Капец блин самое основное
sounds  you take this information Yes here  I
Да звидки вы бере это информацию Да вот
pour it to the Russians in short in the information
россиянам лью короче таке в информацийне
from the TV with the Telegram channel z all there
с телевизора с Telegram канала з всё там
grandmothers are amazed TV young people
бабушки дивляться телевизор молодь
are amazed Telegram channel and they
дивится Telegram канальчик так и вони
will suck it in
всмоктуються
I am not a source and this is so Yes put a
Ясь нере джерела и Цей так Да поставте
like write leave a comment this is very
лайк пишиться залиште комент це дуже
important write on y Telegram right now
важливо пись на й Telegram прямо зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok this  very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through a serious ban and I
нас через срр твый бан и дуже багато
dont show a lot of videos to people sometimes I dont show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams so that
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
we can quickly write links
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться пря
right now and Popik there in telegrams will find
зараз а Попик там в телеграми окрим
videos that are also interesting and useful
видео ще теж е цикава и корисна
information and  we owe you a
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
permanent operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe ah
подпишись ah